{
    "FourAnswers1" : [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "name": "Books",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Who among the following is the author of the novel 'Oliver Twist'?",
                    "TAnswer":  "Charles Dickens",
                    "answers" : ["Charlottie bronte", "EM Forster", "Thomas Hardy",  "Charles Dickens"]
                   
                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "‘Game Changer’ is the name of an autobiography of which sportsperson?",
                    "TAnswer": "Shahid Afridi",
                    "answers" : ["Rahul Dravid","Shahid Afridi","Shane Warne","Yuvraj Singh"]
                      
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "The author of world famous Harry Potter series is?",
                    "TAnswer": "JK Rowling",
                    "answers" : ["Emest Twain","JK Rowling","William Austson","George Orwell"]
                },
                {
                   "id" : 4,
                    "question": " Which among the following books had been written by Barack Obama?",
                    "TAnswer": "The audacity of hope",
                    "answers" : ["What happened ",
                     "The audacity of hope",
                     "Hard Choices ",
                    "Living History"]
                   
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "'Mein Kampf' is the autobiography of which of these?",
                    "TAnswer": "Adolf Hitler",
                    "answers" : ["Vladimir Putin",
                     "Winston Churchill",
                     "Adolf Hitler",
                    "Barack Obama"]
                }
            ]
          
        },


        {
            "id" : 2,
            "name": "Cities",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which city has Europe's tallest skyscraper as of 2021?",
                    "TAnswer": "St. Petersburg",
                    "answers" : ["Moscow",
                    "St. Petersburg",
                     "Paris",
                    "Berlin" ]              

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was the former name of the Indian city of Mumbai?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bombay",
                    "answers" : [ "Mysore",
                    "Madras",
                     "Bangalore",
                     "Bombay"]
                   
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Africa's largest city in terms of population is ...?",
                    "TAnswer": "Lagos",
                    "answers" : ["Cairo",
                     "Lagos",
                     "Luanda",
                    "Botswana"]                   
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which country has two capitals: one formed historically and the other is one by law?",
                    "TAnswer": "Tanzania",
                    "answers" : ["Tanzania",
                    "Switzerland",
                    "Qatar",
                     "Yeman"  ]              
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which capital city has the largest population as of 2021?",
                    "TAnswer": "Beijing",
                    "answers" : ["Beijing",
                    "Rio",
                     "Moscow",
                    "New Delhi" ]         
                }
            ]
        },


        {
            "id" : 3,
            "name": "Nature",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which sea is the largest on Earth?",
                    "TAnswer": "Philippines sea",
                    "answers" : ["Yellow Sea",
                     "Philippines sea",
                   "Black Sea",
                   "Caspian sea"]                   

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which country has the largest number of lakes in the world?",
                    "TAnswer": "Canada",
                    "answers" : ["Finland",
                     "Canada",
                    "Russia",
                   "USA"]
                    

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which river flows through 10 countries?",
                    "TAnswer": "The Danube",
                    "answers" : ["The Tiber",
                     "The River Thames",
                    "The Danube",
                    "The Amazon River"]
                    


                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which month is the calendar autumn in the Southern Hemisphere?",
                    "TAnswer": "March",
                    "answers" : ["March",
                     "February",
                    "September",
                     "July"]
                    


                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which river flows through Rome?",
                    "TAnswer": "The Tiber",
                    "answers" : ["The Ticino",
                     "The Tiber",
                    "The Tanaro",
                    "The Teneso"]
                    

                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 4,
            "name": "Hollywood",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Where is Hollywood located?",
                    "TAnswer": "Los Angeles",
                    "answers" : ["Georgia",
                     "Arizona",
                     "Los Angeles",
                     "Las Vegas" ]                 

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Who among the following has been awarded as the best female actress at the Oscars 2022?",
                    "TAnswer": "Jessica Chastain",
                    "answers" : ["Kristen Stewart",
                     "Jessica Chastain",
                     "Nicole Kidman",
                     " Penelope Cruz"]
                   
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who is the director of 'Wonder women'superhero movie?",
                    "TAnswer": "Patty Jenkins",
                    "answers" : ["Connie Nilsen",
                     "Patty Jenkins",
                     "Alex xavier",
                     "Emily Rotherd "]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which film won the Oscar 2021 for Best Picture?",
                    "TAnswer": "Nomad Land",
                    "answers" : ["Minari",
                     "Nomad Land",
                     "Mank Daag",
                     "The Fire"]               
                    }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What is the place of origin of Batman?",
                    "TAnswer": "Gotham",
                    "answers" : ["Newark",
                     "Gotham",
                     "Nevada",
                     "Hoboken"]  
                         }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 5,
            "name": "Continents",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Largest Suspension bridge (Golden Gate Bridge) is located in North America Continent at?",
                    "TAnswer": "San Francisco",
                    "answers" : ["San Francisco",
                     "Las Vegas",
                     "Los Angeleis",
                     "Ne]w York "]
                         
                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which of the following lakes does not belong to Asia?",
                    "TAnswer":  "Malawi",
                    "answers" : ["Caspian Sea",
                     "Baikal",
                     "Aral Sea",
                     "Malawi"]  
                                 },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which among the following mountains does not belong to Europe",
                    "TAnswer": "Rocky",
                    "answers" : ["Alps",
                     "Pyrenes",
                     "Carpathians",
                     "Rocky"]           },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which is the oldest state in Australia continent?",
                    "TAnswer": "New South Wales",
                    "answers" : ["Canberra",
                     "New South Wales",
                     "Victoria",
                     "Queen]sland"]

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which among the following rivers does not belong to Africa?",
                    "TAnswer": "Colorado",
                    "answers" : ["Congo",
                     "Niger",
                     "Nile",
                     "Colorado"]   
                      }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 6,
            "name": "world cups",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which country is the winner of the ‘2022 FIFA U-17 Women’s World Cup’?",
                    "TAnswer": "Spain",
                    "answers" : ["France",
                     "Spain",
                     "Brazil",
                     "Colombia"]
                             },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "How many times Brazil has won the Football World Cup so far?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["5",
                     "4",
                     "7",
                     "6"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which version of the ICC Men's T20 Cricket World Cup would be played in the year 2022?",
                    "TAnswer": "8th",
                    "answers" : ["10th",
                     "8th",
                     "9th",
                     "7th"]
                },
               {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which country has won the ICC Men's T20 Cricket World Cup title twice?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["India",
                     "West Indies",
                     "Australia",
                     "England"]                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "what was hosted country for rugbhy world cup 2022",
                    "TAnswer": "New Zealand",
                    "answers" : ["South Africa",
                     "England",
                     "New Zealand",
                     "Japan"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 7,
            "name": "Space",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which country has launched its spacecraft to Mars named ‘Hope’?",
                    "TAnswer": "Japan",
                    "answers" : ["Israel",
                     "North Korea",
                     "UAE",
                     "Japan"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "VIPER, which is seen in news regarding space exploration, is a robot proposed by which agency?",
                    "TAnswer": "NASA",
                    "answers" : ["NASA",
                     "ISRO",
                     "ESA",
                     "Roscosmos"
              ]  },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which countries have been elected as President and Co-President of the International Solar Alliance?",
                    "TAnswer": "India and France",
                    "answers" : ["France and Korea",
                     "India and France",
                     "Japan and Korea",
                     "China and Japan"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which planet looks reddish in the night sky?",
                    "TAnswer": "Mars",
                    "answers" : ["Jupiter",
                     "Saturn",
                     "Mars",
                     "Mercury"
          ]          

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which planet has the fastest revolution time?",
                    "TAnswer": "Mercury",
                    "answers" : ["Mercury",
                     "Uranus",
                     "Neptune",
                     "Jupiter"
       ]             
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 8,
            "name": "Defense",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which of the following Missile Systems is developed by the USA?",
                    "TAnswer": "THAAD",
                    "answers" : [" S-400 Triumph",
                     "THAAD",
                     "Barak",
                     "A-135"

    ]            },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "LAC (Line of Actual Control) was settled between india and?",
                    "TAnswer": "Pakistan",
                    "answers" : ["Pakistan",
                     "China",
                     "Bhutan",
                     "Nepal"
          ]      },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Joint exercises between the Air Forces of India and Srilanka are called?",
                    "TAnswer": "Mitra Shakthi",
                    "answers" : ["Hand in Hand",
                     "Yudh Abhyas",
                     "Mitra Shakthi",
                     "Veera"]
                     
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "CORPAT is a Military Exercise between India and which country?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bangladesh",
                    "answers" : ["Japan",
                     "Sri Lanka",
                     "Bangladesh",
                     "Russia"
    ]                

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What was the most famous Russian weapon?",
                    "TAnswer": "AK-47",
                    "answers" : ["AN-602",
                     "AT-74",
                     "AK-47",
                     "AT-18"
             ]   }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 9,
            "name": "Foreign Media",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What was the parent organization of CNN?",
                    "TAnswer": "Warner Bros",
                    "answers" : ["Warner Bros",
                     "Paramount",
                     "Zero Global",
                     "Canopy"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Who is the new CEO of CNN?",
                    "TAnswer": "Chris Licht",
                    "answers" : ["Chris Licht",
                     "Ted Turner",
                     "Reese Dock",
                     "Fleminn Warner"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who was the chairperson of BBC?",
                    "TAnswer": "Richard Sharp",
                    "answers" : ["John Reith",
                     "Richard Sharp",
                     "Alan Dockrell",
                     "Peter Delany"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What does Al Jazeera mean in English?",
                    "TAnswer": "Peninsula",
                    "answers" : ["Peninsula",
                     "Sharpness",
                     "Democracy",
                     "Success"
]                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Where the Time magazine based on?",
                    "TAnswer": "New York",
                    "answers" : ["London",
                     "New York",
                     "Washington",
                     "Paris"
     ]           }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 10,
            "name": "Celebrities",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What was Will Smith's next film in 2022",
                    "TAnswer": "Emancipation",
                    "answers" : ["Emancipation",
                     "The Pursuit",
                     "Hancock",
                     "Invisible man"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Who was the richest actor in 2022",
                    "TAnswer": "Jerry Seinfeld",
                    "answers" : ["Tom Cruise",
                     "Jerry Seinfeld",
                     "Mary-Kate",
                     "Robert De Niro"]
                   
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What movie which Tom Cruise not act?",
                    "TAnswer": "Gentleman",
                    "answers" : ["Jack Reacher",
                     "Mummy",
                     "Gentleman",
                     "Risky Business"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which song does not belong to Ed Sheeran",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["castle on the hill",
                     "thinking out loud",
                     "skin",
                     "A team"   ]        

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Where is rapper Drake originally from",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["USA",
                     "UK",
                     "South Africa",
                     "Canada"
           ]         
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 11,
            "name": "Organizations",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which international organisation has approved 750-billion-euro coronavirus fund, for its member countries?",
                    "TAnswer": "European Union",
                    "answers" : ["G-20",
                     "European Union",
                     "ASEAN",
                     "BIMSTEC"]      
                           },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which country is hosting the Global Youth Climate Summit?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bangladesh",
                    "answers" : ["Oman",
                     "India",
                     "Bangladesh",
                     "UAE"] 
                       },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "The headquarters of World Bank is situated in?",
                    "TAnswer": "Washington",
                    "answers" : ["Brussels",
                     "Berlin",
                     "Washington",
                     "Geneva "]                 

                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "The headquarters of World Health Organization is situated in?",
                    "TAnswer": "Geneva",
                    "answers" : ["California",
                     "Geneva",
                     "Paris",
                     "London"]                  
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "United Nations industrial development organization  was established in?",
                    "TAnswer": "1966",
                    "answers" : ["1967",
                     "1965",
                     "1966",
                     "1968"]
                }
            ]
            
        }
       
        
    ],
    

    "FourAnswers2" : [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "name": "TV shows",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which city name is not used in Money Heist?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bangkok",
                    "answers" : ["Stockholm",
                     "Tokyo",
                     "Lisbon",
                     "Bangkok"
       ]             




                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "In which UK city does Peaky Blinders take place?",
                    "TAnswer": "Birmingham",
                    "answers" : ["Birmingham",
                     "Manchester",
                     "Liverpool",
                     "London"]
                    


                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which actress portrayed Emily Cooper in Emily in Paris?",
                    "TAnswer": "Lily Collins",
                    "answers" : ["Ashley Park",
                     "Lily Collins",
                     "Emilia Clarke",
                     "]Lily James"]
                    



                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who portrays Dr Watson in Sherlock?",
                    "TAnswer": "Martin Freeman",
                    "answers" : ["Martin Freeman",
                     "Benedict Cumberbatch",
                     "Andrew Scott",
                     "Rupert Graves"]                   

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Complete the name of this TV show. “It’s always _____ in Philadelphia”.",
                    "TAnswer": "Sunny",
                    "answers" : ["Rainy",
                     "Cold",
                     "Sunny",
                     "Hot"
                 ]   

                }
            ]
          
        },


        {
            "id" : 2,
            "name": "Countries",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Land of Golden fibre is known as?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bangladesh",
                    "answers" : ["Vietnam",
                     "Indonesia",
                     "Philippines",
                     "Bangladesh"]
                       

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which country has the motto `Liberty, Equality, Fraternity`?",
                    "TAnswer": "France",
                    "answers" : ["The USA",
                     "France",
                     "China",
                     "Russia"
          ]      },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which of these countries is not the European one?",
                    "TAnswer": "Algeria",
                    "answers" : ["Czech",
                     "Algeria",
                     "Hungary",
                     "Denmark"
        ]        },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which country is related to folk music genre Flamenco (songs and dances)?",
                    "TAnswer": "Spain",
                    "answers" : ["Italy",
                     "Spain",
                     "Protugal",
                     "Mexico"
          ]      }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which European country is also known as Holland?",
                    "TAnswer": "The Netherlands",
                    "answers" : ["Spain",
                     "Greece",
                     "Italy",
                     "The Netherlands"
   ]             }
            ]
        },


        {
            "id" : 3,
            "name": "Rivers",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "How many rivers in srilanka?",
                    "TAnswer": "103",
                    "answers" : ["101",
                     "98",
                     "103",
                     "97"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which is world largest river?",
                    "TAnswer": "Amazon",
                    "answers" : ["Amazon",
                     "Niger",
                     "Nile",
                     "Orion"
              ]  },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which country has maximum rivers?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bangladesh",
                    "answers" : ["India",
                     "Srilanka",
                     "Bangladesh",
                     "China"
      ]          },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which is India's largest river?",
                    "TAnswer": "Indus",
                    "answers" : ["Ganga",
                     "Bramaputhra",
                     "Indus",
                     "Mahanadee"]           
                     }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question":"Which river has most number of dams?",
                    "TAnswer": "Ganga",
                    "answers" : ["Ganga",
                     "Bramaputhra",
                     "Indus",
                     "Mahanadee"]
               }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 4,
            "name": "Bollywood",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "The IIFA Awards of 2022 was which edition of the IIFA awards?",
                    "TAnswer": "22nd",
                    "answers" : ["19th",
                     "21st",
                     "22nd",
                     "18th"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which movie has won the Best Feature Film award at 68th National Film Awards 2022?",
                    "TAnswer": "Soorarai Pottru",
                    "answers" : ["Jersey",
                     "Tanhaji",
                     "RRR",
                     "Soorarai Pottru"
   ]             },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "In the Indian movie 'Gold' (2018), Akshay kumar's film name was?",
                    "TAnswer": "Tapas Das",
                    "answers" : ["Ubayan singh",
                     "Tapas Das",
                     "Bhalaji Rao",
                     "Tripathi Pandey"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is highest-grossing Indian film worldwide?",
                    "TAnswer": "Dangal",
                    "answers" : ["Baahubali 2",
                     "Dangal",
                     "RRR",
                     "KGF 2"
         ]       }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which movie is based on Indian hockey team on their first Olympic gold?",
                    "TAnswer": "Gold",
                    "answers" : ["Chak De",
                     "MS Dhoni",
                     "Gold",
                     "Lagaan"
         ]              
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 5,
            "name": "Islands",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is the famous island near singapore?",
                    "TAnswer": "Baali",
                    "answers" : ["Baali",
                     "Booran",
                     "Monali",
                     "Santory"

         ]       },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which is the smallest island in the world?",
                    "TAnswer": "Nauru",
                    "answers" : ["Kauai",
                     "Nauru",
                     "Sicily",
                     "Monaca"
            ]    },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which is the smallest island in Asia?",
                    "TAnswer": "Maldives",
                    "answers" : ["FIJI",
                     "Bahamas",
                     "Maldives",
                     "Seyshells"
      ]          },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which country has most islands?",
                    "TAnswer":  "Sweden",
                    "answers" : ["Maldives",
                     "Philiipines",
                     "singapore",
                     "Sweden"
]                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which is island of pearls?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bahrain",
                    "answers" : ["Hawaii",
                     "Bhahamas",
                     "Bahrain",
                     "Andaman"
      ]          }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 6,
            "name": "Olympic",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Who is the host of 2024 Olympics?",
                    "TAnswer": "Paris",
                    "answers" : ["Tokyo",
                     "Paris",
                     "Sydney",
                     "Berlin"

           ]     },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "How many times has Russia hosted the Olympics?",
                    "TAnswer": "2",
                    "answers" : ["2",
                     "1",
                     "3",
                     "0"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "How many countries are in the Olympics?",
                    "TAnswer": "206",
                    "answers" : ["203",
                     "198",
                     "203",
                     "206"]
                },
               {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who won Olympic men's 100m 2020?",
                    "TAnswer": "Marcell Jacobs",
                    "answers" : [" Andre De Grasse",
                     "Marcell Jacobs",
                     "Fred Kerley",
                     "Noah Lyles"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who won Olympic women's 100m 2020?",
                    "TAnswer": "Elaine Thompson",
                    "answers" : ["Elaine Thompson",
                     "Shelly-Ann",
                     "Shericka Jackson",
                     "Shelinda Herah"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 7,
            "name": "Earth",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "The seasonal contrasts are maximum in?",
                    "TAnswer": "Mid latitudes",
                    "answers" : ["Low latitudes",
                     "Mid latitudes",
                     "Sub tropics",
                     "High Latitudes"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "For a time difference of two hours, the longitudinal distance will be equal to?",
                    "TAnswer": "30°",
                    "answers" : ["15°",
                     "30°",
                     "45°",
                     "60°"
                      ]                
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What is the difference between the Local time and Greenwich time one degree longitude?",
                    "TAnswer": "4 min",
                    "answers" : ["2 min",
                     "4 min",
                     "6 min",
                     "8 min"

             ]   },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which star is nearest to the Earth?",
                    "TAnswer": "Sun",
                    "answers" : ["Alpha Centauri",
                     "Pole star",
                     "Chitra",
                     "Sun"
  ]                  

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "The International Date Line passes through?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bering strait",
                    "answers" : ["Bering strait",
                     "Gibraltar strait",
                     "Florida strait",
                     "Malacca strait"]

                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 8,
            "name": "Presidents",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Ibrahim Boubacar Keita, who has recently resigned, was the President of which country?",
                    "TAnswer": "Mali",
                    "answers" : ["Mali",
                     "Indonesia",
                     "Maldives",
                     "Qatar"

       ]         },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "U.S President Joe Biden announced to end the country’s support for Saudi-led military operations in which country?",
                    "TAnswer": "Yemen",
                    "answers" : ["Iran",
                     "Yemen",
                     "Sudan",
                     "Afghanistan"
         ]       },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who was the youngest person to become president of the United States?",
                    "TAnswer": "John F Kennedy",
                    "answers" : ["John F Kennedy",
                     "Theodore Roosevelt",
                     "Bill Clinton",
                     "Barack Obama"]
                    



                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "How long is the presidential term in the USA? ",
                    "TAnswer": "4 Years",
                    "answers" : ["5 Years",
                     "4 Years",
                     "6 Years",
                     "3 Years"
      ]          }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What is the name of the US President’s office? ",
                    "TAnswer": "The Oval Office",
                    "answers" : ["The White House",
                     "The Dallas",
                     "The Oval Office",
                     "The Balfour"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 9,
            "name": "Local Media",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is the oldest TV channel in Sri Lanka?",
                    "TAnswer": "The ITN",
                    "answers" : ["Rupavahini",
                     "The ITN",
                     "Rangiri",
                     "TNL"

      ]          },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What is the first private TV channel in Sri Lanka?",
                    "TAnswer": "TNL",
                    "answers" : ["Sirasa",
                     "TNL",
                     "Siyatha",
                     "Swarnavahini"
      ]          },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What is the first newspaper in Sri Lanka?",
                    "TAnswer": "Lakmini Pahana",
                    "answers" : ["Lankarawaya",
                     "Lakmini Pahana",
                     "Siyadesa",
                     "Randiwa"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is the first radio channel in Sri Lanka?",
                    "TAnswer": "Radio Colombo",
                    "answers" : ["Rajarata sewaya",
                     "Radio Colombo",
                     "Lakhada",
                     "Radio ceylon"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What is the first English paper in Sri Lanka?",
                    "TAnswer": "The Times of Ceylon",
                    "answers" : ["The colombo",
                     "Lanka Times",
                     "The Times of Ceylon",
                     "Daily Mirror"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 10,
            "name": "Billionars",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Who is the 3rd Richest person in the World",
                    "TAnswer": "Gautam Adani",
                    "answers" : ["Jeff Bezos",
                     "Bernard Arnault",
                     "Gautam Adani",
                     "Bill Gates"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Who is the world's richest singer?",
                    "TAnswer": "Kanye West",
                    "answers" : ["Madonna.",
                     "Rihanna",
                     "Kanye West",
                     "P-Diddy."
 ]               },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who is co-founder & chairman of LVMH?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bernard Arnault",
                    "answers" : ["Warren Buffett",
                     "Bernard Arnault",
                     "Larry Page",
                     "Jeff Bezos"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who is CEO of Berkshire Hathaway?",
                    "TAnswer": "Warren Buffett",
                    "answers" : ["Warren Buffett",
                     "Bernard Arnault",
                     "Larry Page",
                     "Jeff Bezos"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who was known as the `Oracle of Omaha`",
                    "TAnswer": "Warren Buffett",
                    "answers" : ["Warren Buffett",
                     "Bernard Arnault",
                     "Larry Page",
                     "Jeff Bezos"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 11,
            "name": "film production companies",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which movie that paramount pictures films produced?",
                    "TAnswer": "Top Gun: Maverick",
                    "answers" : ["Top Gun: Maverick",
                     "F9",
                     "Beast",
                     "Jurrasic world"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was the highest grossing film for Universal Pictures?",
                    "TAnswer": "Jurassic World",
                    "answers" : ["Minions",
                     "Beast",
                     "Jurassic World",
                     "F9"
      ]          },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Where are universal films made?",
                    "TAnswer": "California",
                    "answers" : ["California",
                     "Chicago",
                     "Houstan",
                     "Texsas"
    ]            },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What Disney movie has sold the most?",
                    "TAnswer": "The Lion King",
                    "answers" : ["Frozen II",
                     "The Lion King",
                     "Incredibles 2",
                     "Frozen"]

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What is Netflix's most watched show of all time?",
                    "TAnswer": "Squid Game",
                    "answers" : ["Squid Game",
                     "Stranger Things",
                     "Dahmer",
                     "Money-heist"]
 
                }
            ]
        }
       
        
    ],


    "ThreeAnswers1" : [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "name": "Cricket",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which country will host the 2023 cricket world cup?",
                    "TAnswer": "India",
                    "answers" : ["England",
                     "India",
                     "South Africa"]


                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "International Cricket Council (ICC) headquarters is located in?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["Dubai",
                     "London",
                     "Melbourne"]
                    

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who was the First Pakistani Player to have a hundred in T20Is?",
                    "TAnswer": "Ahmed Shehzad",
                    "answers" : ["Mohammad Hafeez",
                     "Farkar Zaman",
                     "Ahmed Shehzad"
                  
]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who is the bowler which fastest to get 100 ODI wickets?",
                    "TAnswer": "Rashid Khan",
                    "answers" : ["Rashid Khan",
                     "Mitchell Starc",
                     "Shahid Afridi"
                  

 ]               }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Australia won The Ashes series, 2017-18 by?",
                    "TAnswer": "4-0",
                    "answers" : ["3-2",
                     "3-1",
                     "4-0"]
                    
                }
           ] 
          
        },


        {
            "id" : 2,
            "name": "Social media",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "what social network is considered the most popular for business to business marketing",
                    "TAnswer": "LinkedIn",
                    "answers" : ["Facebook",
                     "LinkedIn",
                     "Orkut"]
                    
                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What feature announced by Facebook in 2013?",
                    "TAnswer": "Clickable hashtags",
                    "answers" : ["Facebook Home",
                     "Facebook Graph Search",
                     "Clickable hashtags"        ]  

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "When was the first launch of Facebook?",
                    "TAnswer": "In 2004",
                    "answers" : ["In 2004",
                     "In 2003",
                     "In 2005"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is the name of a fee-based communications tool that aims to (connect everyone) while at work announced by Facebook?",
                    "TAnswer": "Workplace",
                    "answers" : ["LinkedIn",
                     "Oculus Connect",
                     "Workplace"]

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which of the following is not Twitter subsudary?",
                    "TAnswer": "Snapchat",
                    "answers" : ["Periscope",
                     "Vine",
                     "Snapchat"]

                }
            ]
           },


        {
            "id" : 3,
            "name": "Players",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What year did Ronaldo first won his Ballon d'Or and FIFA World Player of the Year awards?",
                    "TAnswer": "2008",
                    "answers" : ["2009",
                     "2008",
                     "2010"                              

                ]},
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Who was 2nd most top goal hitter in football?",
                    "TAnswer": "Josef Bican",
                    "answers" : ["Josef Bican",
                     "Lionel Messi",
                     "Cristiano Ronaldo"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who is the youngest Ballon d'Or winner?",
                    "TAnswer": "Ronaldo Nazario",
                    "answers" : ["Ronaldo Nazario",
                     "Lionel Messi",
                     "Johan Cruyff"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who is the 1 best basketball player of all time?",
                    "TAnswer": "Michael Jordan",
                    "answers" : ["Wilt Chamberlain",
                     "Michael Jordan",
                     "Bill Russell"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who is the youngest player in the NBA in 2022-23",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["Will O'Neal",
                     "Larry Bird",
                     "Jalen Duren"]
                }
         ]   
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 4,
            "name": "Universities",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Where was Oxford university situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "United Kingdom",
                    "answers" : ["United Kingdom",
                     "USA",
                     "Walse"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which university was not at USA?",
                    "TAnswer": "Columbia University",
                    "answers" : ["Harvard University",
                     "Columbia University",
                     "Stanford University"
   ]             },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which university that Tiger woods consider as notable alumini?",
                    "TAnswer": "Stanford University",
                    "answers" : ["University of Cambridge",
                     "Stanford University",
                     "University of Calif]ornia"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which university Mark Zuckerberg dropshis higher education?",
                    "TAnswer": "Harvard University",
                    "answers" : ["Harvard University",
                     "Oxford University",
                     "Cambridge University"
    ]            }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which university awarded an honorary doctorate to Bill Gates but never completed his bachelor's degree?",
                    "TAnswer": "Harvard University",
                    "answers" : ["Harvard University",
                     "Oxford University",
                     "Cambridge University"
    ]            }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 5,
            "name": "Web series",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What was web series that Mr. Bean act?",
                    "TAnswer": "Man vs. Bee",
                    "answers" : ["Man vs. Bee",
                     "God's man",
                     "Big Mouth"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was the Japanease web series out of there?",
                    "TAnswer": "SPY×FAMILY",
                    "answers" : ["Vincenzo",
                     "SPY×FAMILY",
                     "Melo Is My Nature"]
                },
               {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What was genre of `See` web series",
                    "TAnswer": "Sci-fi",
                    "answers" : ["Romance",
                     "Sci-fi",
                     "Horror"]
                },
                {
                   "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which one of these are indian thriller series?",
                    "TAnswer": "Family man",
                    "answers" : ["Helstorm",
                     "Trapped",
                     "Family man"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What is the third television series in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU) produced by Marvel Studios",
                    "TAnswer": "Loki",
                    "answers" : ["She-hulk",
                     "Loki",
                     "Ms.Marvel"]
                }
            
      ]  }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 6,
            "name": "Flags",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "How many all the flags in the world?",
                    "TAnswer": "193",
                    "answers" : ["195",
                     "198",
                     "193"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "How many flags are on the moon?",
                    "TAnswer": "6",
                    "answers" : ["4",
                     "8",
                     "6"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which is the oldest flag in the world?",
                    "TAnswer": "of Denmark",
                    "answers" : ["of Sweden",
                     "of Denmark",
                     "of France"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which country flies the largest flag?",
                    "TAnswer": "Mexico",
                    "answers" : ["USA",
                     "Mexico",
                     "Brazil"]
                    
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What is the most unique flag?",
                    "TAnswer": "Nepal",
                    "answers" : ["Nepal",
                     "Mexico",
                     "Brazil"]
                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 7,
            "name": "Dates",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What was date for World Cancer Day",
                    "TAnswer": "Feb 4",
                    "answers" : ["Jan 5",
                     "Feb 4",
                     "Apr 6"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was the International Women's Day",
                    "TAnswer": "Mar 8",
                    "answers" : ["Feb 12",
                     "Mar 8",
                     "Jun 15"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What was the World Health Day",
                    "TAnswer": "Apr 7",
                    "answers" : ["Apr 7",
                     "Mar 8",
                     "Jun 15"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What was the Independence Day of India",
                    "TAnswer": "Aug 15",
                    "answers" : ["Apr 7",
                     "Mar 8",
                     "Aug 15"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What was the World Food Day",
                    "TAnswer": "Oct 16",
                    "answers" : ["Apr 7",
                     "Oct 16",
                     "Aug 15"]
                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 8,
            "name": "Scooby doo",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is Scooby-Doo's legal name?",
                    "TAnswer": "Scoobert Doo",
                    "answers" : ["Scoobert Doo",
                     "Scooby-Dooby-Doo",
                     "Scooby Doo"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What race is Scooby-Doo?",
                    "TAnswer": "Great Dane",
                    "answers" : ["Great Dane",
                     "English Mastiff",
                     "Saint Bernard"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who is the oldest in Scooby-Doo?",
                    "TAnswer": "Shaggy",
                    "answers" : ["Fred",
                     "Shaggy",
                     "Velma"]
                },
                {
                   "id" : 4,
                    "question": "When was the First appearance of Scooby-Doo? ",
                    "TAnswer": "1969",
                    "answers" : ["1994",
                     "1969",
                     "1982"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who was the original voice actor for Shaggy?",
                    "TAnswer":"Casey Kasem",
                    "answers" : ["Neil Fanning",
                     "Danny Bage",
                     "Casey Kasem"]
                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 9,
            "name": "Harry potter",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "How many novells in Harry-potter series",
                    "TAnswer": "7",
                    "answers" : ["6",
                     "8",
                     "7"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What spell did Harry use to kill Lord Voldemort?",
                    "TAnswer": "Expelliarmus",
                    "answers" : ["Expelliarmus",
                     "Expecto Patronum",
                     "Avada Kedavra"
                  ]  
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What position does Harry play on his Quidditch team?",
                    "TAnswer": "Seeker",
                    "answers" : ["Bludger",
                     "Chaser",
                     "Seeker"]
                    

                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What was the name of the Black family’s house elf?",
                    "TAnswer": "Kreacher",
                    "answers" : ["Kreacher",
                     "Dobby",
                     "Winky"]
                    
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which element is associated with Hufflepuff?",
                    "TAnswer": "Earth",
                    "answers" : ["Fire",
                     "Earth",
                     "Water"]
                    

                }
           ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 10,
            "name": "Russia",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which of the following Russian cities is farthest North?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["Moscow",
                     "St. Petersburg",
                     "Magadan"
                    
           ]     },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which of these rivers is the longest?",
                    "TAnswer": "Lena",
                    "answers" : ["Amur",
                     "Dnieper",
                     "Lena"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What is Russia's parliament called, which is equivalent to America's Cogress?",
                    "TAnswer": "Duma",
                    "answers" : ["Duma",
                     "Knesset",
                     "Diet"]
                    
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "The strait separating Russia from Alaska is?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bering strait",
                    "answers" : ["Bering strait",
                     "Torres strait",
                     "Luzon strait"]

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Russia does not share its boundary with?",
                    "TAnswer": "Polland",
                    "answers" : ["Mongolia",
                     "Polland",
                     "Kazakastan"]

                }
            ]
       }
       
        ,


        {
            "id" : 11,
            "name": "Prison Break",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Who was the real actor name as Poseidon?",
                    "TAnswer": "Jacob Ness",
                    "answers" : ["Peter Stormare",
                     "Jacob Ness",
                     "Robert Knepper"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Lincoln Burrows is accused or killing?",
                    "TAnswer": "Terrence Steadman",
                    "answers" : ["Mark Steadman",
                     "Terrence Steadman",
                     "Rsymond Steadman"

            ]    },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "LanIn which country is Michael in jail for the fifth season?d",
                    "TAnswer":  "Yemen",
                    "answers" : ["Iraq",
                     "Yemen",
                     "Saudi Arabia"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What was Michael’s job before he was arrested?",
                    "TAnswer": "structural engineer",
                    "answers" : ["structural engineer",
                     "architect",
                     "Computer engineer"

             ]   }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who says `I will gun you down Scofield`?",
                    "TAnswer": "Captain Bellick",
                    "answers" : ["Paul Kellerman",
                     "Agent Mahone",
                     "Captain Bellick"
                  ]  
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
               
    ,

    "ThreeAnswers2" : [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "name": "Rugbhy",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "How many points is a penalty kick worth ?",
                    "TAnswer": "3 points",
                    "answers" : ["5 points",
                     "4 points",
                     "3 points"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which word is  often use for rugby field?",
                    "TAnswer": "Pitch",
                    "answers" : ["Pitch",
                     "Venue",
                     "course"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What was the full time of rugby match?",
                    "TAnswer": "80 min",
                    "answers" : ["90 min",
                     "100 min",
                     "80 min"]
                },
                {
                   "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who was the highest point scorer in rugby?",
                    "TAnswer": "Dan Carter",
                    "answers" : ["Dan Carter",
                     "Jonny Wilkinson",
                     "Owen Farrell"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "How many players in a rugby team?",
                    "TAnswer": "15",
                    "answers" : ["13",
                     "15",
                     "16"]
                }
            ]
          
        },


        {
            "id" : 2,
            "name": "Novels",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Who wrote book called `Yuganthaya`",
                    "TAnswer": "Martin Wickramasinghe",
                    "answers" : ["Mahagamasekara",
                     "Martin Wickramasinghe",
                     "W.A Silva"

              ]  },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which book was not belong to `Mahagamasekara`",
                    "TAnswer": "Kaliyugaya",
                    "answers" : ["Prabuddha",
                     "Tuṇmaṇhandiya",
                     "Kaliyugaya"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who is the father of modern Sinhala literature?",
                    "TAnswer": "Martin Wickramasinghe",
                    "answers" : ["Mahagamasekara",
                     "Martin Wickramasinghe",
                     "W.A Silva"
               ] },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is the 1st novel in Sri Lanka?",
                    "TAnswer": "Meena",
                    "answers" : ["Viragaya",
                     "Meena",
                     "Kaliyugaya"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What is the most read novel?",
                    "TAnswer": "The Harry Potter Series",
                    "answers" : ["Animal Farm",
                     "The Lord of The Rings",
                     "The Harry Potter Series"

   ]             }
            ]
        },


        {
            "id" : 3,
            "name": "singers",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "which was not a song of kasun kalhara?",
                    "TAnswer": "sanda Pahana",
                    "answers" : ["Radical Premaya",
                     "Adara Malwala ",
                     "sanda Pahana"
                 
]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which was not a song album of Rookantha gunathilaka?",
                    "TAnswer": "Lassanai Adare",
                    "answers" : ["Lassanai Adare",
                     "Maaime Idan",
                     "Adara Mal Pawane"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "which of song be a duet in original singing?",
                    "TAnswer": "Ahasin eha",
                    "answers" : ["Anganaawo",
                     "Ahasin eha",
                     "Gimhaana Kale"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What was the first song album of BNS?",
                    "TAnswer": "Vasanthaye",
                    "answers" : ["Tharunyaye",
                     "Vasanthaye",
                     "Neththara"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": " Who was sung by සේල ඇන්දම මාල බැන්දම song?",
                    "TAnswer": "WAYO",
                    "answers" : ["Marians",
                     "WAYO",
                     "BILLY With 242"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 4,
            "name": "Famous Companies",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Where are the headquarters of Tesla situated in?",
                    "TAnswer": "Texas",
                    "answers" : ["Chicago",
                     "Texas",
                     "Houston"]

                },
                {
                   "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was country Mercedez benz based for?",
                    "TAnswer": "Germany",
                    "answers" : ["Germany",
                     "France",
                     "Italy"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who was founder of Huawei Technologies?",
                    "TAnswer": "Ren Zhengfei",
                    "answers" : ["Kia Shenzhen",
                     "Liang Hua",
                     "Ren Zhengfei"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is Apple's latest update?",
                    "TAnswer": "Apple's iOS 16",
                    "answers" : ["Apple's iOS 17",
                     "Apple's iOS 15",
                     "Apple's iOS 16"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who was the CEO OF Google LLC?",
                    "TAnswer": "Sundar Pichai",
                    "answers" : ["Satya Nadella",
                     "Sundar Pichai",
                     "Parag Agrawal"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 5,
            "name": "Airports",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which is worlds biggest airport?",
                    "TAnswer": "King Fahd Airport",
                    "answers" : ["King Fahd Airport",
                     "Atlanta Airport",
                     "Heathrow Airport"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What is the world's busiest airport in 2022?",
                    "TAnswer": "Dubai",
                    "answers" : ["Dubai",
                     "Heathrow",
                     "Atlantas"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "what country mostly tourists come from to dubai airport 2021",
                    "TAnswer": "India",
                    "answers" : ["India",
                     "France",
                     "China"]
                },
                {
                   "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is the second biggest airport in the world.",
                    "TAnswer": "Denver",
                    "answers" : ["Dubai",
                     "Heathrow",
                     "Denver"]
                }
                ,
               {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What was world's Best Airport for Passenger Security Screening in 2022.",
                    "TAnswer": "Zurich",
                    "answers" : ["Dubai",
                     "Heathrow",
                     "Zurich"]
                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 6,
            "name": "symbols",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What was the national flower of india?",
                    "TAnswer": "Lotus",
                    "answers" : ["Lotus",
                     "Temple flower",
                     "Orchid"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was the symbol of ferrai logo?",
                    "TAnswer": "Horse",
                    "answers" : ["Tiger",
                     "Horse",
                     "Eagle"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which country's flag displays a white cross in the centre of a square red field?",
                    "TAnswer": "Switzerland",
                    "answers" : ["Poland",
                     "Finland",
                     "Switzerland"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which of the flag that not include crescent moon?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["Singappore",
                     "Iran",
                     "Algeria"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What was National Motto of insia?",
                    "TAnswer": "Satyameva Jayate",
                    "answers" : ["Jana Gana Mana",
                     "Vande Mataram",
                     "Satyameva Jayate"]
                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 7,
            "name": "Years",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What the year that happened 9/11 attack on World Trade Center?",
                    "TAnswer": "2001",
                    "answers" : ["2000",
                     "2002",
                     "2001"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What the year that happened Fukushima Daiichi Nuclear Disaster?",
                    "TAnswer": "2011",
                    "answers" : ["2014",
                     "2011",
                     "2009"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What the year that happened Reveals Secrets by Snowden?",
                    "TAnswer": "2013",
                    "answers" : ["2015",
                     "2013",
                     "2011"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What was the year that Trump Elected as president?",
                    "TAnswer": "2016",
                    "answers" : ["2018",
                     "2016",
                     "2014"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What was the year that Bin Laden Killed?",
                    "TAnswer": "2011",
                    "answers" : ["2012",
                     "2008",
                     "2011"]
                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 8,
            "name": "Tin Tin",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is the name of the residence that the Captain and Professor Calculus live in?",
                    "TAnswer": "Marlinspike",
                    "answers" : ["Marlinspike",
                     "Picaros",
                     "Labrador"
                     
           ]         
                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What are the Captain's favourite two words?",
                    "TAnswer": "Blistering barnacles",
                    "answers" : ["Great snakes",
                     "Blubbering blizzards",
                     "Blistering barnacles"        ]             

 
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What is Captain Haddock's first name?",
                    "TAnswer": "Archibald",
                    "answers" : ["William",
                     "Archibald",
                     "Herbert"
                                    ]              
                   
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What does Professor Calculus hate being called, or being told he acts like, by the Captain?",
                    "TAnswer": "A goat",
                    "answers" : ["An ass",
                     "A goat",
                     "A horse"]
            
 
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who is Tintin's biggest enemy?",
                    "TAnswer": "Rastapopoulos",
                    "answers" : ["Muller",
                     "Rastapopoulos",
                     "Colonel Sponz"  ]                 

                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 9,
            "name": "Pirates of caribians",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Whose blood did pirates need to break the curse?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["Will Turner",
                     "Elizabeth Swann",
                     "Jack Sparrow"
                    
]


                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Where does the royal family of Elizabeth Swann live and rule?",
                    "TAnswer": "Port Royal",
                    "answers" : ["Isla da Muerte",
                     "Port Royal",
                     "Port Arthur"]
 
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What was the common disease on the set?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["Seasickness",
                     "Malaria",
                     "Flu"   
                                   ]                        
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "When was the first movie of the series released?",
                    "TAnswer": "2003",
                    "answers" : ["2001",
                     "2003",
                     "2002"  ] 
                    
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What did Depp seriously changed in his look for the role of Jack Sparrow?",
                    "TAnswer": "Teeth",
                    "answers" : ["Teeth",
                     "Nose",
                     "Hair"
                                              ]            
                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 10,
            "name": "China",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "When did China get back Hong Kong?",
                    "TAnswer": "1997",
                    "answers" : ["1977",
                     "1982",
                     "1997"]
 
                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which country is considered a renegade province by China?",
                    "TAnswer": "Taiwan",
                    "answers" : ["North Korea",
                     "Taiwan",
                     "South Korea"
                  
            ]    },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which nation does not share a border with China?",
                    "TAnswer": "Taiwan",
                    "answers" : ["Mongolia",
                     "Tajikistan",
                     "Taiwan"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is the national game of china?",
                    "TAnswer":"Table Tennis",
                    "answers" : ["Badminton",
                     "Hockey",
                     "Table Tennis"]

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What was the Border name of India and China?",
                    "TAnswer": "McMohan Line",
                    "answers" : ["BharatChe Line",
                     "McMohan Line",
                     "Radcliffe Line" ]
                }
            ]
        }

        ,


        {
            "id" : 11,
            "name": "Games of thrones",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "How many kingdoms are there in Westeros continent?",
                    "TAnswer": "7",
                    "answers" : ["5",
                     "7",
                     "3"]


                },
                {
                   "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which novel series is Game of Thrones based on?",
                    "TAnswer": "A Song of Ice and Fires",
                    "answers" : ["The Winds of Winter",
                     "Nightflyers",
                     "A Song of Ice and Fires"
      ]            

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What is the fictional place where most of the Game of Thrones is set?",
                    "TAnswer": "Seven Kingdoms of Westeros",
                    "answers" : ["Seven Kingdoms of Westeros",
                     "The Drone Areas",
                     "Island of Madagascar"]
                  
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is the last name of Bastards in Dorne?",
                    "TAnswer": "Sand",
                    "answers" : ["Soil",
                     "Sand",
                     "Sea"   ]                

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who shot the burning arrow at Hoster Tully's Funeral?",
                    "TAnswer": "Brynden Tully",
                    "answers" : ["Edmure Tully",
                     "Lord Karstark",
                     "Brynden Tully"]
                    
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
         
    ,

    "TwoAnswers1" : [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "name": "Economy",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which country is the leading exporter of Basmati Rice to the global market as of 2021-22?",
                    "TAnswer": "India",
                    "answers" : ["China",
                     "India"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which of the following types of economy describes the economy of the UK?",
                    "TAnswer": "A mixed economy",
                    "answers" : ["A mixed economy",
                     "A command economy"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "In the short-run, which of the following always gets smaller as output increases?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["Short-run marginal cost",
                     "Average fixed cost"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "The main watch dog of international trade is?",
                    "TAnswer": "WTO",
                    "answers" : ["WTO",
                     "IMF"]

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id]" : 5,
                    "question": "Which country get the highest ranking in the lastest list published by World Bank for GDP per capital?",
                    "TAnswer": "Luxembourg",
                    "answers" : ["Luxembourg",
                     "Norway"]

                }
            ]
          
        },


        {
            "id" : 2,
            "name": "Israel",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is depicted on the emblem of the State of Israel?",
                    "TAnswer": "Menorah",
                    "answers" : ["David's star",
                     "Menorah"]
 

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which country supported Israel in the development of Iron Dome?",
                    "TAnswer": "USA",
                    "answers" : ["USA",
                     "Russia"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which star appears on the flag of Israel?",
                    "TAnswer": "Star of David",
                    "answers" : ["star of Bethlehem",
                     "Star of David"]
                    
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which is the currency of Israel?",
                    "TAnswer": "Shekel",
                    "answers" : ["Shekel",
                     "Rouble"]
 
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which is the official language of Israel?",
                    "TAnswer": "Hebrew",
                    "answers" : ["Arabic",
                     "Hebrew"]

                }
            ]
            
        },


        {
            "id" : 3,
            "name": "Michael Jackson",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which was Michael Jackson’s first album?",
                    "TAnswer": "Got to be There",
                    "answers" : ["Off the Wall",
                     "Got to be There"]
                

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Which movie did Michael Jackson contribute a song to as the soundtrack?",
                    "TAnswer": "ET",
                    "answers" : ["Poltergeist",
                     "ET"]
                    
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which Michael Jackson music video features dancing zombies?",
                    "TAnswer": "Thriller",
                    "answers" : ["Thriller",
                     "Beat it"]
 
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "How many singles did Michael Jackson release throughout his career?",
                    "TAnswer": "13",
                    "answers" : ["18",
                     "13"]

                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What was the name of Michael Jackson’s ranch?",
                    "TAnswer": "Neverland",
                    "answers" : ["Neverland",
                     "Xanadu"]

                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 4,
            "name": "Gossips",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Who was recently married couple in bollywood?",
                    "TAnswer": "Ranbir-Aliya",
                    "answers" : ["Ranbir-Aliya",
                     "Varun-Natasha"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was latest movie of Siddarth malhothra?",
                    "TAnswer": "Thank god",
                    "answers" : ["Bedhiya",
                     "Thank god"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who is loving couple in Shershah movie?",
                    "TAnswer": "Sid-Kiara",
                    "answers" : ["Sid-Aliya",
                     "Sid-Kiara"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who is the main actor of LIGER?",
                    "TAnswer": "Vijay D'konda",
                    "answers" : ["Tiger Sheroff",
                     "Vijay D'konda"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which was upcoming movie of SRK?",
                    "TAnswer": "Dunki",
                    "answers" : ["Dunki",
                     "Yodha"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,

        {
            "id" : 5,
            "name": "Local map",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Where is the province which foul point situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "Eastern",
                    "answers" : ["Northern",
                     "Eastern"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Where is the province which chundikulam bird santuary situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "Northern",
                    "answers" : ["Northern",
                     "Eastern"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What is the highest village in Sri Lanka?",
                    "TAnswer": "Shanthipura",
                    "answers" : ["Padiyathalawa",
                     "Shanthipura"]
                },
                {
                    "id]" : 4,
                    "question": "Where was pigeon island situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "Tricomalee",
                    "answers" : ["Puttalam",
                     "Tricomalee"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Where was Kovalam Lighthouse situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "Karaitivu",
                    "answers" : ["Muthur",
                     "Karaitivu"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }
        ,

        {
            "id" : 6,
            "name": "Lasith Malinga",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What was the country which malinga get 4 wickets in 4 balls in T20?",
                    "TAnswer": "New Zealand",
                    "answers" : ["South Africa",
                     "New Zealand"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was T20 world-cup title that Srilanka win under Malinga Captancy?",
                    "TAnswer": "2014",
                    "answers" : ["2012",
                     "2014"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What was ODI series which malinga played before retirement?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bangladesh",
                    "answers" : ["Bangladesh",
                     "West Indies"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "When Malinga announced his retirement from all forms of cricket?",
                    "TAnswer": "2021 SEP",
                    "answers" : ["2021 SEP",
                     "2021 DEC"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "How many hat-tricks did malinga have in ODI cricket",
                    "TAnswer": "3",
                    "answers" : ["4",
                     "3"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }
        ,

        {
            "id" : 7,
            "name": "Buildings",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is the world's largest office building?",
                    "TAnswer": "Pentagon",
                    "answers" : ["Grand Kremlin",
                     "Pentagon"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Where is Red square building located?",
                    "TAnswer": "China",
                    "answers" : ["Japan",
                     "China"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "In which US city is the White House?",
                    "TAnswer": "Washington",
                    "answers" : ["NewYork",
                     "Washington"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "In which Indian state is the Taj Mahal located?",
                    "TAnswer": "Uttar Pradesh",
                    "answers" : ["Uttar Pradesh",
                     "Maharashtra"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Out of these buildings,which is in france?",
                    "TAnswer": "Louvre Pyramid",
                    "answers" : ["Verona arena",
                     "Louvre Pyramid"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }  ,

        {
            "id" : 8,
            "name": "Nobel Prices",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which of the following awards is also known as Alternative Nobel Prize?",
                    "TAnswer": "Right Livelihood",
                    "answers" : ["Pulitzer",
                     "Right Livelihood"]
                    

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Who was first African-American woman to win the Nobel Prize for Literature?",
                    "TAnswer": "Toni Morrison",
                    "answers" : ["Jennifer Doudna",
                     "Toni Morrison"]
                 
                    
            },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which of the following awards is known as Mathematicians' Nobel Prize?",
                    "TAnswer": "Abel Prize",
                    "answers" : ["Rolf Nevanlinna Prize",
                     "Abel Prize"]
                 

                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who is the most famous Nobel Prize winner?",
                    "TAnswer": "Martin Luther King",
                    "answers" : ["Martin Luther King",
                     "Benjamin Julius"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who was both Oscar and a Nobel Prize winner?",
                    "TAnswer": "Bob Dylan",
                    "answers" : ["Linus Pauling",
                     "Bob Dylan"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }  ,

        {
            "id" : 9,
            "name": "Tennis",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which Grand Slam tournament is annually held in January?",
                    "TAnswer": "Australian Open",
                    "answers" : ["French Open",
                     "Australian Open"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What is it called when the score is 40 – 40?",
                    "TAnswer": "Deuce",
                    "answers" : ["Draw",
                     "Deuce"]
                },

                
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which tennis player won runners-up in Men’s Singles at 2021 Wimbledon?",
                    "TAnswer": "Matteo Berrettini",
                    "answers" : ["Matteo Berrettini",
                     "Andy Murray"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "How many Grand Slam titles has Roger Federer won so far?",
                    "TAnswer": "20",
                    "answers" : ["20",
                     "22"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Novak Djokovic comes from which nation?",
                    "TAnswer": "Siberia",
                    "answers" : ["Siberia",
                     "Spain"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }  ,

        {
            "id" : 10,
            "name": "Leaders",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Who is the Emperor of Japan",
                    "TAnswer": "Naruhito",
                    "answers" : ["Naruhito",
                     "Akihito"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "How many Sovereign states in the world with a monarch as head of state.",
                    "TAnswer": "43",
                    "answers" : ["37",
                     "43"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who was the Princess of Denmark?",
                    "TAnswer": "Princess Mary",
                    "answers" : ["Princess Isabella",
                     "Princess Mary"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Who is the Queen of Jordan now?",
                    "TAnswer": "Rania Al-Abdullah",
                    "answers" : ["Salma bint-Abdullah",
                     "Rania Al-Abdullah"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Who was the Crown Prince of Saudi Arabia",
                    "TAnswer": "Salman Al-Saud",
                    "answers" : ["Salman Al-Saud",
                     "Khalid Bin-Salman"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }  ,

        {
            "id" : 11,
            "name": "Foreign Tunnels",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What was tunnel that links Swiss and Italy?",
                    "TAnswer": "Simplon",
                    "answers" : ["Severn",
                     "Simplon"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was tunnel that links Honshu with Hokkaido?",
                    "TAnswer":"Seikan",
                    "answers" : ["Haiken",
                     "Seikan"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Where was longest tunnel was situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "Norway",
                    "answers" : ["Norway",
                     "Finland"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Which country has most tunnels?",
                    "TAnswer": "Norway",
                    "answers" : ["Norway",
                     "Germany"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which country has underwater tunnel?",
                    "TAnswer": "China",
                    "answers" : ["China",
                     "UAE"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
              
    ,

    "TwoAnswers2" : [
        {
            "id" : 1,
            "name": "Tourism",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Where is Borobudur Temple situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "Indonesia",
                    "answers" : ["Thailand",
                     "Indonesia"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Where is the Chichen Itza situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "Mexico",
                    "answers" : ["Mexico",
                     "Colombia"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which is not a country that nearby red sea?",
                    "TAnswer": "Sudan",
                    "answers" : ["Libiya",
                     "Sudan"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Where was Goa situated geographycally in india?",
                    "TAnswer": 7.50,
                    "answers" : ["Southeastern coast",
                     "southwestern coast"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Where was Bali island situated?",
                    "TAnswer": "Indonesia",
                    "answers" : ["Indonesia",
                     "Singappore"]
                }
            ]
          
        },


        {
            "id" : 2,
            "name": "Australia",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is the capital of australia",
                    "TAnswer": "Canberra",
                    "answers" : ["Sydney",
                     "Canberra"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was the largest city in australia",
                    "TAnswer": "Sydney",
                    "answers" : ["Sydney",
                     "Melbourne"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "When Australia got independance from UK?",
                    "TAnswer": "Jan 1",
                    "answers" : ["Jan 1",
                     "Aug 25"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What was the capital of Victoria state in Australia?",
                    "TAnswer": "Melbourne",
                    "answers" : ["Adelade",
                     "Melbourne"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "How many times commanwealth games organized in Australia?",
                    "TAnswer": "5",
                    "answers" : ["4",
                     "5"]
                }
            ]
        },


        {
            "id" : 3,
            "name": "Shakira",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What does the name Shakira mean?",
                    "TAnswer": "graceful" ,
                    "answers" : ["beautiful",
                     "graceful" ]                 

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was the name of Shakira's first album?",
                    "TAnswer": "Magia",
                    "answers" : ["Magagia",
                     "Magia"]
                    
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which Colombian soap opera did Shakira star in?",
                    "TAnswer": "El Oasis",
                    "answers" : ["El Nacho",
                     "El Oasis" ]                                  
                    
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What was the name of Shakira's debut single in English?",
                    "TAnswer": "Whenever,Wherever",
                    "answers" : ["Whenever,Wherever",
                     "Objection"]
                                      
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Which country is Shakira from?",
                    "TAnswer": "Colombia",
                    "answers" : ["Colombia",
                     "Mexico"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,


        {
            "id" : 4,
            "name": "Sayings",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "`The only thing we have to fear is fear itself`. who said that?",
                    "TAnswer": "Roosevelt",
                    "answers" : ["Roosevelt",
                     "Muhammad Ali"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Float like a butterfly, sting like a bee. who said that?",
                    "TAnswer": "Muhammad Ali",
                    "answers" : ["Martin Luther",
                     "Muhammad Ali"]
                },
                {
                    "i]d" : 3,
                    "question": "The future belongs to those who prepare for it today.who said that?",
                    "TAnswer": "Marie Curie",
                    "answers" : ["Marie Curie",
                     "Mahatma Gandhi"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "You miss 100% of the shots you don't take.who said that?",
                    "TAnswer": "Wayne Gretzky",
                    "answers" : ["Thomas Edison",
                     "Wayne Gretzky"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "Don't cry because it's over; smile because it happened.who said that?",
                    "TAnswer": "Dr. Seuss",
                    "answers" : ["Dr. Seuss",
                     "Jesus Christ"]
                }
            ]
        }
        ,

        {
            "id" : 5,
            "name": "world map",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which African lake, named for a British Queen, does the Equator pass through?",
                    "TAnswer": "Lake Victoria",
                    "answers" : ["Lake Diana",
                     "Lake Victoria"]

                },
                {
                    "id]" : 2,
                    "question": "Which of these countries located above equator?",
                    "TAnswer": "Phillipines",
                    "answers" : ["Mauritius",
                     "Phillipines"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What name is given to 180° longitude due to the spherical shape of the earth ?",
                    "TAnswer": "International Date Line",
                    "answers" : ["International Date Line",
                     "Capricorn line"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "How many countries are in Capricorn Line?",
                    "TAnswer": "10",
                    "answers" : ["12",
                     "10"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "which country located between Tropic of Cancer and Capricorn?",
                    "TAnswer": "Cambodia",
                    "answers" : ["Taiwan",
                     "Cambodia"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }

        ,

        {
            "id" : 6,
            "name": "Shane Warne",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "what was the Jersey number of him in AUS team?",
                    "TAnswer": "23",
                    "answers" : ["19",
                     "23"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What duration of his active contribution to national team?",
                    "TAnswer": "15 years",
                    "answers" : ["17 years",
                     "15 years"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "What was the year that Warne was inducted into the ICC Cricket Hall of Fame",
                    "TAnswer": "2013",
                    "answers" : ["2011",
                     "2013"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What was best bowling performance in test cricket?",
                    "TAnswer": "8/71",
                    "answers" : ["8/71",
                     "7/58"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "How many test wickets in his career?",
                    "TAnswer": "708",
                    "answers" : ["712",
                     "708"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }       ,

        {
            "id" : 7,
            "name": "Towers",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Which country has most skyscrapers?",
                    "TAnswer": "China",
                    "answers" : ["Russia",
                     "China"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What was 2nd highest skycraper in the world?",
                    "TAnswer": "Merdeka tower",
                    "answers" : ["Merdeka tower",
                     "Shanghai Tower"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Which city has most skyscrapers in Europe?",
                    "TAnswer": "Paris",
                    "answers" : ["Paris",
                     "Germany"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Where was lotte tower located?",
                    "TAnswer": "Seoul",
                    "answers" : ["Seoul",
                     "Tokyo"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What was the upcoming highest skyscraper in dubai?",
                    "TAnswer": "Creek Tower",
                    "answers" : ["Uptown Tower",
                     "Creek Tower"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }       ,

        {
            "id" : 8,
            "name": "Awards",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "Booker Prize is given in the field of?",
                    "TAnswer": "Fiction writing",
                    "answers" : ["Fiction writing",
                     "Science"]
                    

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "The first Indian to win the ICC ODI Player of the Year (2007) Award is",
                    "TAnswer": "MS Dhoni",
                    "answers" : ["Saurav Ganguly",
                     "MS Dhoni"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Orange prize is given in the field of",
                    "TAnswer": "Literature",
                    "answers" : ["Literature",
                     "Music"]
                   

                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Grammy Award is given in the field of?",
                    "TAnswer": "Music",
                    "answers" : ["Literature",
                     "Music"]
 
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "In which field is Pulitzer Prize awarded for outstanding work ?",
                    "TAnswer": "Literature-Journalism",
                    "answers" : ["Literature-Journalism",
                     "Science-Technology"]
                   
                }
       ]     
        }       ,

        {
            "id" : 9,
            "name": "Chess",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is the name of the rating system that measures a player’s strength?",
                    "TAnswer": "Elo",
                    "answers" : ["Elo",
                     "Alo"  ]                 

                },
                {
                    "]id" : 2,
                    "question": "The quickest possible checkmate is in:?",
                    "TAnswer": "2 moves",
                    "answers" : ["2 moves",
                     "3 moves"]
                    

                },
                {
                   "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Other than world champion, what is the highest title a chess player can earn?",
                    "TAnswer": "Grand master",
                    "answers" : ["Super master",
                     "Grand master"]
                                    
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "Where did chess originate?",                
                    "TAnswer": "India",
                    "answers" : ["China",
                     "India"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "How many moves was the longest [known] chess game in history?",
                    "TAnswer": "269",
                    "answers" : ["237",
                     "269"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }       ,

        {
            "id" : 10,
            "name": "Parliments",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "What is a parliament of Japan called?",
                    "TAnswer": "Diet",
                    "answers" : ["Diet",
                     "Seoul"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "Who was Prime Minister of the United Kingdom?",
                    "TAnswer": "Rishi Sunak",
                    "answers" : ["Rishi Sunak",
                     "Kamila Sen"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                    "question": "Who has the monarch of British Parliment?",
                    "TAnswer": "Charles III",
                    "answers" : ["Charles III",
                     "Charles II"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "How many members of U.S. parliament are there?",
                    "TAnswer": "535",
                    "answers" : ["535",
                     "456"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "How many Senators in U.S. parliament now?",
                    "TAnswer": "100",
                    "answers" : ["120",
                     "100"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }       ,

        {
            "id" : 11,
            "name": "Local tunnels",
            "cato": [
                {
                    "id" : 1,
                    "question": "How many railway tunnels are there from Colombo to Badulla?",
                    "TAnswer": "46",
                    "answers" : ["46",
                     "43"]

                },
                {
                    "id" : 2,
                    "question": "What is the longest railway tunnel in Sri Lanka.",
                    "TAnswer": "Poolbank",
                    "answers" : ["Poolbank",
                     "Pattipola"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 3,
                   "question": "“Singimale tunnel” lies between Hatton and --------- railway stations.",
                    "TAnswer": "Kotagala",
                    "answers" : ["Kotagala",
                     "walimada"]
                },
                {
                    "id" : 4,
                    "question": "What is the third longest and the highest railway tunnel in Sri Lanka",
                    "TAnswer": "Pattipola",
                    "answers" : ["Kotagala",
                     "Pattipola"]
                }
                ,
                {
                    "id" : 5,
                    "question": "What is the second longest railway tunnel in Sri Lanka",
                    "TAnswer": "Moragalla",
                    "answers" : ["Moragalla",
                     "Kotagala"]
                   
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}    
    
    

    

    
       
        
    

  
